Guide to the William R. Rambo Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Material, 1961-1991; Accession ARCH-1997-093
  - Chron file, 1961-1991
    - 1970 Nov (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 1970 Dec (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 1971 Jan (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 1971 Feb (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 1971 Mar (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 1971 Apr (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 1971 May-Jun (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 1971 Jul (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 1971 Aug (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - 1971 Sep-Dec (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 1972 Jan-Feb (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 1972 Mar-May (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 1972 Jun-Aug (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Memo and note re natural disaster preparation, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Index re overhead costs (1969-1970 letters), 1991 Feb 8 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Student unrest, 1966-1971
    - -1, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - -1, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - -1, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - -2M (1), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - -2M (2), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - -3P, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - -1P, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - -2M, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - -2M (tape of “Rambo Song”), 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - -3, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - -4 (1), 1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - -4 (2), 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - -5, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - -6, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - -7, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - -8M, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - -9, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - -10, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - -10 (transcript of US Senate Hearings), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 1, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 2, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 3, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 1P, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 2, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - 3, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Photo Album - AEL during sit-in of April 1969; Encina April 1969; vandalism at Durand Building early 1970. Most photos taken by Lloyd Provan, the University photographer., Undated (Box 9)